Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.thirt Mss.B.B61.inventory13
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents V
  - Van de Water, Marjorie (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 2p
  - Van Doren, Carl (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 July 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 June 30; 1p
    - From Dunn, L.C. (to VanDoren, Mark), 1938 Jan. 12
    - To Dunn, L.C. (from Van Doren, Mark)
    - See Margin of Dunn, L.C. (to VanDoren, Mark), 1938 Jan. 12
  - Van Gieren, Ira (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1897 Mar. 8
  - Van Kauduict, W. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1891 July 4
  - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 20
  - Van Meter, I. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 15; 1p
  - Van Ness, Elsie (Elise) (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 29; 1p
  - Van Norden, O. H. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 28; 1p
  - Van Sickle, J.V. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1926 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 13; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1928, 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 22; 1p
  - Van Tyne, C. H. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 4; 1p
      Enc: NY Peace Committee
  - Van Veen, Stuyvesant (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Sep. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 12; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to C.R.B. Educational Foundation), 1937 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1939 July 13; 1p
  - Van Vleck, J. H. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 11; 1p
  - Vandenhoek & Rupeecht (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 13; 1p
  - Vanderford, Kenneth H. (Box 92)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., Jan. 1938
  - Vanikoff, M. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 25; 1p
      - See carbon copy, 1937 Dec. 7; 1p
  - Varegny, Henry de (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 9
  - Varela M.C., Gerardo (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p
  - Varney, John (Box 92)
    - (open letter)
    - Enc. with Nadejena, Lydia, 1942 Mar. 25; 1p
  - Varuniella, Leite de (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 11; 1p
  - Vasconcellos, L. de (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1923 May 28; 1p
  - Vassar, E. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 19; 6p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1933, 3p
  - Vatter, E. (Box 92)
    - Direktion des Museums der Columbia University, 1926 Mar. 25; 2p
  - Vaughan, George (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 2; 1p
  - Vaughn, W. C. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Columbia Univ. Graduate School. Dean, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Veblen, Oswald (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23
    - See Boas, F. (to Pound, R.), 1923 May 23
    - From Boas, 1933 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 20; 1p
  - Veblen, T. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 12; 1p
  - Vedin, A. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1909 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 15
  - Veis, Helmut (Box 92)
    - See Veis, Lore, 1938 July 8
  - Veis, Lore (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1938 July 8; 1p
  - Veit, B. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 10
  - Veit & Co. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1914 May 25
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1889 June 8
    - To Boas, 1912 June 27
    - To Boas, 1912 July 5
    - To Boas, 1912 July 12
    - To Boas, 1912 July 13
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 9
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 8
    - From Lehmann, Rudolf, 1913 Oct. 11
    - From Lehmann, R., 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 30
    - To Lehmann, Rudolf, 1913 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 28
  - Velasir, L. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 17; 1p
  - Velikovsky, Immanuel (Box 92)
    - From Boas Enc:, 1940 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas Enc:, 1940 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas Enc:, 1940 Mar. 25; 1p
    - From Boas Enc:, 1940 Mar. 28; 1p
    - From Boas Enc:, 1940 Apr, 29; 1p
  - Velte, Henry F. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 14; 1p
  - Velten, H. V. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Sep, 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 2; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1937, 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 17; 1p
  - Venezuela. Ministerio de Educacion Nacional (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Vereinigung Carl Schurz (Box 92)
    See Ferber, Gertrud
    See Erkelenz
  - Vereinigung Wissenschaftlicher Verlager (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 21
  - Verlag der Neuen Generation (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 10; 1p
  - Verlagsbuchhandlung Julius Springer (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 10; 2p
  - Vermillion Conference (Box 92)
    - See National research council, 1931 Sep. 10
  - Vernon, H. W. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 18; 1p
  - Verschner, O. v. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 4; 1p
  - Verspreet, R. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1920 May 9; 4p
  - Verwept, C. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1907 May 17
  - Verzeichnis Amerikanischer Fortsetzungewerke (Box 92)
    - Found at end of 1920, 4p
    - Found at end of 1920, 1920 Feb
  - Veümann, W. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 5; 1p
  - Viault, E. R. (Box 92)
    - OPEN LETTER, 1918 Apr.; 1p
    - Enc. originally with Barnes, H.E., 1918 July 8
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Vickers, Rose M. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 22; 2p
  - Vidaver, Sidney J. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 5; 1p
  - Vidgoff, Ben (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 21
  - Vienna Anthropological Society (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 27; 1p
  - Viereck, George Sylvester (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1917 June 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 July 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 21; 1p
    - Enc. Viereck, G.S. (to Bliven, B.), 1935 Oct. 1
    - To Bliven, B. Jr., 1935 Oct. 1; 1p
    - Enc. with Viereck, G.S., 1935 Oct. 21
  - Viereck, Louis (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 21; 1p
  - Viereck Publishing Co. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 4
  - Viereck's - The American Weekly (Box 92)
    See Viereck, George Sylvester
  - Vietor, J. B. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, E. L., 1904 June 20; 1p
  - Vietor, Karl (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Vieweg, Friedrich und Sohn (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 20; 2p
  - Vigodsky, S. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1928 July 25; 1p
  - Viking Club (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1897 Jan. 14
  - Viking Press (Box 92)
    - See Huebsch, B. W., 1935 Mar. 21
  - Vilhuber, Ernest (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p
  - Villard, Harold G. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, E. L., 1905 Feb. 2; 1p
  - Villard, Henry (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1899 Nov. 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1900 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1918 Sep. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1896 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1897 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 21; 2p
  - Villard, Mrs. Henry (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 3
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 16
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 6
    - From Boas, 1908 June 6
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1910 May 12
    - From Boas, 1910 May 27
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 July 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas Enc., 1928 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 May 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 July 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 22
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 19
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 10; 7p
    - To Boas, 1908 June 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 25
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1910 May 10
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 May 14
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Sep. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Oct. 6; 1p
    - Enc. Kerkhof, Karl Paper, 1922 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p
      See Boas, F. (open letter)
    - Found at end of Dec. 1939
      - Enc., 1940 July 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 May 22; 1p
    - To Germanistic Society of America (W.A. Braun), 1919 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To LaFrentz, F. W., 1933 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Lawson, J. H., 1934 Dec. 30
    - From Peabody, G. F., 1912 May 13
  - Viltum, Murriel A. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
  - Vincens, Juan (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 28; 3p
  - Vincent, C. B. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 4; 1p
  - Vincent, George E. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 17; 1p
      Enc. list of Medical Journals
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1920 July 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 July 26; 1p
  - Vincent, J. M. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1892 Dec. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1892 Dec. 30; 2p
  - Vinton, C. C. (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 19; 1p
  - Vintschger, G. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 5; 1p
  - Virchow, Hans (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1895 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1895 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1895 Oct. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 2
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 June 10
    - To Boas, 1913 June 14
    - To Boas, 1913 June 18
    - To Boas, 1913 July 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1916 June 7
    - Death notice, 1934 Aug. 5; 2p
  - Virchow, Lisbeth (Mrs. Hans) (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1913 June 14; 2p
  - Virchow, Rudolf (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1883 June 3
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1893 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1901 Dec. 20
  - Virchow, W. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1921 Jan. 5; 2p
  - Vital, Joseph (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 5
    - From Boas, 1909 July 2
    - From Boas, 1909 Oct 30
    - To Boas, 1909 July 3
  - Viva, Jorge A. (Box 92)
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 13
  - Vladivostoc - State University (Box 92)
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 11; 1p
  - Vodicka, Otokar (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p
  - Voegelin, Carl F. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 11; 1p
    - Found at end of1933 Dec., 1937 Aprl 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 28; 1p
  - Voehringer, E. F. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 14; 1p
  - Voelkel, T. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 27; 1p
  - Voelkischer Beobachter (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 24; 1p
  - Vogeler, Adolf (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1883 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 28; 3p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 14
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 19
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 24
    - To Boas, 1932 Sep. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1933 May 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 16; 2p
      - Death, 1935 Aug. 5; 1p
  - Vogeler, Anna (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 5; 4p
  - Vogeler, W. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 9
  - Vogelstein, Ludwig (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 22; 1p
  - Vogt, Hans (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 17; 1p
  - Vogt, Oskar (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 22; 1p
  - Volel, Edvard (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 1; 1p
    - Enc. with McConnell, H.O., 1941 Feb. 8
  - Volhard (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1938 Sep. 22; 1p
  - Volkert, J. F. (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 1
  - Volksfront (Box 93)
    - See Deutschamerikanischer Kulturverhand, 1938 Dec. 17
  - Volz, Louis (Box 93)
    - To Boas, 1906 July 11; 1p
  - Volz, W. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 21; 1p
  - Voorhis, Harold O. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 3
    - Enc. Addressed to the rector Karl-Franzens University, 1932 Nov. 3
    - To Karl-Franzens University, 1932 Nov. 3; 1p
    - Attached to letter to Boas, F. From Voorhis, Harold O., 1932 Nov. 3
    - To Saslow, G., 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - Enc. with Cattell, McKeen, 1936 Sep. 22
  - Vorhaus, D. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 8; 1p
  - Vorhis, C. van (Box 93)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), 1932 Apr. 14
  - Vorks, H. R. (Box 93)
    - To Miss Andrews, 1912 May 23; 2p
  - Vos, B. J. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 3; 1p
  - Vossische Zeitung, Editor (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 14; 2p
  - Voth, H. R. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 May 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 June 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 July 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Aug. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 Dec. 8
    - To Boas, 1925 May 8; 5p
    - To Boas, 1925 June 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 June 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 21; 6p
    - To Boas, 1925 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 19; 3p
    - To Andrews, H. A., 1911 Dec. 15
  - Vowell, A. T. (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1901 Oct. 7; 2p
  - Voynich, E. L. de (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 18; 4p
  - Voynow, Rose Cantor (Box 93)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 28; 1p